Thank you for watching
Noridaka Noridu
Noridaka Halloween Party 2023
The game competition between teams in costume is finally at its climax!
The final game of the night, with the losers terrified of the shocking punishment that awaits them, is...
Azie the Halloween Costume Play Girl is flying!
All teams will try to jump rope in their costumes!
The number of times you jump is the point of the game, and you can make a big comeback!
The more you jump, the more you win!
You can make a big difference!
The winning team will be rewarded with candy!
The losing team will be punished with a Halloween-like game.
And now.......................................
He's here today, too.
Thank you very much!
The first team is the ghost team!
How many times can you jump?
Tamura, why don't you put the pressure on?
That's right. 50.
If you fly 50 times, you're probably pretty good.
50 jumps.
Iwamoto... but in the past... they couldn't jump rope at all.
That's right, if you do it the way you did in elementary school, you won't be able to do it.
Why did I think I couldn't do it?
I have to raise my legs more than I thought I would.
I want to do my best.
I see.
I've never jumped a long rope before?
It's my first time.
Well, I wish you the best of luck. I see.
Yes, sir.
Iwamoto-san.
A praying mantis.
A praying mantis, Breamieux.
It's flying.
Let's go jump-rope cosplay!
Yes, sir!
Haunted team!
All right, let's go!
Ready?
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Ten.
That's good.
That's pretty good.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Sixteen.
Seventeen.
Eighteen.
Wow, that's great.
This is pumpkin team pressure
No, no, no.
Twenty-nine.
Oh, great.
Yes, sir.
Oh, my gosh.
No, this is pretty good.
I got stuck at the end.
But we were all at our limits.
That's for sure.
How did you jump?
Iwamoto, what's wrong?
My leg!
They hurt...
It hurts.
That was a close one.
I flew in those shoes.
But...
Thirty times.
Thirty.
30 times. That's amazing.
Can the lead pumpkin team get past the ghost team?Can the Leading Pumpkin Team Surpass the Ghost Team?
That dinosaur of a bow tree.
Well, it's pretty compact now, isn't it?
It's all tucked away.
Yes, sir.
That's pretty good.
The delicatessen is easy to fly, isn't it?
The delicatessen...
He still moves like a champ.
You can do well in any event... as a delicatessen worker.
That's why he works so hard.
I'm going to have to fly about 40 more times to beat you in the other games.
That's for sure.
Yes.
I want to win, right?
But I'm totally looking forward to it.
What's that?
To go over.
Oh, to go over.
He's so determined!
We're down to our socks!
Go, pumpkin team!
Oh, this is the platform!
I've been thinking about it.
Let's go, pumpkin team!
Come on, Pumpkin Team!
Let's go for it, pumpkin team!
Let's go for it!
Will the pumpkin team led by Umezawa make a big comeback?
Seino! heave, ho!
The winning haunted team will receive an assortment of Aloin snacks!
And what awaits the losers?
The penalty game... is that they all have to get together and take a pie bazooka to the face at the same time.
That's a lie!
What kind of punishment?
And we'll all do it together.
Single file.
One line!
Pai Bazooka!
What is the most powerful weapon in the history of the world, the pie bazooka?
We're ready, Mr. Himura.
What's this?
It's a pai bazooka for 8 people at the same time!
It's the Dracula Quiz of Takistan.
Isn't this the most amazing thing you've ever done?
We have to do this, just because we lost a little.
That's right!
This is crazy, Yoda.
It's big. How fast are you going to give it to me?
They're going to take your head off.
This is really dangerous.
Mr. Himura, isn't this scary from my side?
No, it's scary.
Isn't this scary? When it's pointed at you... This doesn't scare you? You said it's pointed at you.
It's pointed at me.
Okay, then.
Why? Why? Why?
Why why why why?
Why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why.
Kaki, you look like Mickey. You're so cute.
I'm scared.
I'm scared. I don't know what to do.
Hey, but we'll all get one together.
Hey.
You're scary
I think I'm gonna cry now, Soma
No, I'm scared
Oh, Kaki, I'm sorry, can I take your place, Mr. Himura?
Kaki.
No, no, no, no.
It's a punishment. I'm sorry, Kaki.
Oh, no.
Endo, it's totally fine.
No, no, no.
What was she like today?
I'm totally fine, the little deli girl.
You're scaring me.
I really might not make it.
Maybe I really can't.
Then we lose.
Okay, let's set sail for 8 simultaneous pie bazookas
Countdown!
Wait, wait, wait. Wait, wait.
It's okay. It's delicious. It's okay.
- Let's go! Five, four, three, two, one, fire!
- Whoo!
- Whoo! Whoo!
- That's great!
- Fire!
Fire!
No way!
No!
Fire!
Oh, shit!
Wait a minute!
That's it in one second!
Isn't that amazing?
Yoda!
I was hitting the hat!
I thought something was missing.
What's there?
That hurt.
What? You look like a raccoon.
Um, someone punched me in the cheek.
It was good.
Everyone got hit once. Just a little bit.
You're all so light.
How was the persimmon?How was the persimmon?
Sweet.
Sweet? It was good.
It's good.
Delicious.
Wait a minute, Shibata's smiling all the time.
Fun.
Fun?
It was fun.
Fun? Fun?
It's Halloween. It's fun, right?
Umea.
How was it?
Well, the candy was good, but...
But in terms of variety, this is definitely better.
Yum!
It's great.
I see what you mean.
I'm glad we didn't lose.
Are you sure you're okay?
What?
You're doing it so fast your face is gonna fly off.
Yeah, it's not so good. We should probably stop airing it.
It's an aquatic club, so it's great.
You really can't see this class on TV right now.
Don! I'm Banana Manes, your host for Nogizaka Construction Workshops.
I'm Banana Manes, your host for Nogizaka Chan.
Nogizaka-chan!
What the hell are you doing? What are you doing already?
Everybody's Version
Today.
We have two teams, one with clothes on and one without.
Mr. Himura, please announce today's plan.
Let's go.
Don Sotheby's.
Nogizaka46 has been known to spill things on the stage.
This time, the Donksas will compete in a variety of events to determine the Donksa Queen of Nogizaka.
First of all, let's start with the Donkusas, or rather, the Donkusas who spill things.
I wouldn't say "Donksasai".
But, you know, when you're all together and everyone's going "wow" and only one of you spills it...
It's loose in the hand.
It's called "donkusai.
I think she's a queen. Already.
This place is already a contender for the championship.
I'd like to nominate you.
Next, Nana Inoue.
What?
This one's also a spill.
She soaked this area.
We've had some episodes.
But I'm probably the worst of the bunch.
Don't you think I'm a bit of a donk?
I was surprised to be chosen.
Then, Yoda.
Yoda, in case you were wondering.
Weapons
Weaponry is donkish.
What do you mean by that? What do you mean?
But, you know, when you're sleeping and you hit the stairs with a bang...
Don't you think that's disgusting?
But I can climb trees, I can swim, I can climb mountains.
Climb mountains?
It's nothing.
I'm a natural donkusa.
Oh my God, I think he might be a contender.
Then the oysters!
Oysters are up for "crass donks.
Messy.
I heard that she does her makeup all at once.
She's pretty good at drawing.
But he's also a good cook.
He's kind of crass.
That's part of it.
So all I have to do is win the competition?
And be the last with this many people?
I mean, isn't this really crass?
But when I saw this group, I thought it would be okay.
That's why they're here.
I'm sure that's what they all think.
And Tutui-Tutui-Tutui-Tutui-Tutui-Tutu.
Tutsui is that toro-son dongsa.
Tutujis have this image of donksa.
Oh, really?
Yes, really.
Yeah, she's kind of quiet, so I get the image of her as a donk.
He looks kind of donkish.
No, but he's pretty quick on the uptake. No, but it's pretty quick on the flip side.
When he's not showing his backside, he's just cracking up.
Maybe because of the way I look or the way I talk.
But I'm fast behind the scenes.
Where's the back?
From where?
The moment I take the mic, it's behind the scenes.
You're all calm and collected and donk-sucking.
Oh, yeah.
That's not good, is it?
It's a donkusa.
I'm sure you'll include this in the mix, too.
Donksa commenting on the body-set.
I know what you mean.
I know what you think of the end too.
I have an image of donksa.
I don't think you can understand it in one go? I don't get it.
I'm explaining.
I'm trying to explain it.
Don't say that.
Donkse.
Then Ikeda
Yes, sir.
Here's another trosso donkusa.
Oh, it looks like donkusa.
Well, I talked about this project with Saki-san yesterday.
I told her we're the ones in uniforms.
So you were chosen?
I was in jersey today.
What's the point of that meeting? What's the point of that meeting?
Nakanishi
Nakanishi is the weakest in the athletic polarity.
That's so stupid.
That's right.
Nakanishi.
Don't you think you're stinky?
Is that so?
In all the projects we've done so far...
The speed it takes to remember is what's donkey-sucky.
What was that?
But I have good instincts, so I think I understand the rules pretty quickly.
I don't know if I can do it even if I understand the rules.
I don't know if I can do it.
I'm squirming!
Someone's going to be the Donksa Queen
That's nice.
I've got it... I've got it...
Looks strong
Eh, I see.
Nakanishi is.
A contender?
Me?
Oh... I see.
What about Kaede Sato?
She's kind of nice.
She's good at sports.
She's just not good at holding food, but everything else is normal.
There was one more food thing.
That's so weird... Yakusayo!
After this, the Dongsa Festival is about to kick off.
Now then, let's get started. Mr. Himura, please compete first.
Let's move the luggage smoothly!
No, no, no!
No, no, no! Luggage!
Hazle!
No!
This is a one-on-one race in which players compete to see how long it takes to move everything on their table to the table on the other side of the table.
The first match-up was between the two main players, Kaede Sato and Dokuto.
The first matchup was between the two main contenders, Kaede Sato and Inoue Dokusei.
Looking at the way these two players are playing, I thought they might have an advantage in the second half of the game, so I asked them to wear blindfolds.
I see.
Now, Mr. Himura, please go to the site and tell me if I'm cheating or something.
I understand.
Yes, I will.
The loser of this game will suddenly receive 3 points, Inoue.
Yes, sir.
This is important.
Do you think you can do it?
Yes, it's possible. I'm not that worried.
I see.
NagataWelcome back. What do you think?
I feel like this game itself is being made fun of.
No, no, no.
You are better.
This tournament is for you, today.
Surely you can carry this over there.
No, no, no.
No, no, no. No, no.
Um, if you drop anything else, please judge me, Mr. Himura. He wants me to come back properly.
Of course, of course. I'm very strict.
If I drop it and fall back, I'll go back and take it with me again.
OK, OK, OK.
We carried a variety of items, including small snacks, paper and pen bundles, and water in cups.
The race started to see what kind of arrangements would be made to carry them.
Okay, let's get started.
Let's go.
Oh, this looks bad.
You've already dropped something.
Can you hit it?
Go back, go back. Go back. Go back. Come back.
Go back, go back.
I'll pick it up and go back in.
Len, this is so strong.
This, look, look, look.
So calm. That's great.
I'm gonna spill what I'm holding.
Oh, my God.
I have no idea what's going on.
It's down, it's down. It's down. It's down. It's down. It's down. I'm down. I'm down.
Fell. Fell.
You fell.
Your hand is too sweet.
You fell again.
Here, here, here, here. This one, this one. This one.
This one.
Photo scene.
Ah. Ahh.
Ball dropped, ball dropped.
I don't have to look at Inoue.
There's a lot of candy over there, too.
I don't care if it's candy.
Sato, who was in his element from the beginning, spilling the ball all over the place with his speed and gravity.
And Inoue, who's just so polite.
Who will win the race?
It's surprisingly good.
Did you drop any snacks? Are you okay?
Maybe one over here.
Yay, yay, yay, yay, yay.
We do this kind of thing, don't we?
Watch out, watch out, watch out. Are you okay? This is the last one.
There's one candy bar. There's one candy bar.
Last one.
There's a piece of candy on the floor.
I told you to wait a minute.
You said it angrily, didn't you?
So, Inoue wins. Kaede Sato gets 3 points for the rocker.
Next, Trosaw Ikeda vs. Bukio Soyoda
Ikeda, how's it going? Well, we just had a strategy meeting.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
In my head, in my head...
I don't want to lose to Yoda.
I'm going to be very careful and deliberate.
Careful, careful, careful.
Now let's get ready for Yoda Ikeda's challenge.
Let's go!
Let's go! Here we go.
That's it.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
Oh!
Oh! Oh!
That's a good one.
No, it's good.
Oh, this is smart.
No, I took it like this.
I was going to do it.
Yeah, I was gonna do it.
OK!
Oh, really?
Oh, yeah!
Dosai! Dosai!
We got him! We got him! We got him!
It's time.
Again! Again!
Wow, that's a lot of dirt.
This is really dirt!
It's so thick!
A pond you want to carry all at once with an umbrella.
In the meantime, it seems to go back and forth many times, carrying it a little bit at a time.
Which is more efficient?
I see.
So this is how they go about it.
It's all at once. This one goes all at once.
Cuer rate
The neck of the foot fell off the leg bone.
Yes! This, this, this!
Despair, now!
Exclusive!
How exclusive!
What an exclusive!
Ikeda's umbrella unexpectedly collapsed and he lost a lot of time!
However, Yoda's small transport did not speed up the race, and the race was a huge battle!
How is this possible?
But if we get there early, we won't know yet!
Yoda has to hurry!
What's that? What's this?
Oh!
Oh! Which way?
Uh, which way? I got it!
I got it wrong!
Oh!
Now that's a real tie!
No, which one is it?
Which is it?
They let go of each other's hands.
It's a toss-up!
He said he's going to move it over here, but since it's broken or misshapen...
Ikeda loses.
He loses!
Yoda wins!
Yoda wins! Yoda wins!
Now, let's move on to the next competition!
Oh, wait a minute, what's with that attitude?
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
What? Are you chewing gum?
Because you called me a turtle.
Because I was called a turtle?
I can't help it now. Next, Mr. Kimura, please.
Let's go!
Gum balloons!
Yes!
I did it! That's what I thought!
We're going to blow up bubblegum balloons for the camera, and you're going to compete with each other in size.
In order of the smallest balloon size, five winners get the donksa point this time!
The point is, the kids who are donks can't even make a good balloon.
Oh, I know!
Nakanishi
I just blew up a balloon at home the other day. I feel like I can do it.
Did you?
It's not gum.
Balloons? I did think you just said "balloon" too.
But I thought you meant gum.
But you really meant balloons.
Have you guys ever done this before?
What do you think?
This.
I have.
If you've never done it, you probably can't do it.
I'm really good at it.
Okay, then. Okay, then.
You can't blow up a balloon, but you can't blow up bubble gum.
Oh, really? Then it works.
Am I not allowed to practice this?
No.
Don't do this.
Don't do it here.
If you do it here, you'll get the donk point.
Absolutely not.
Yoda tried to cheat a little bit.
He tried to take the loophole, the loophole, the loophole.
Who do you want to go first?
Well, the number one hitter is a little hard to get to.
Oooh, kaki! That's a good one.
So Kaki tries her hand at making balloon gum!
Three.
Two. Two.
One.
Can you do it?
Yes, it's done.
But...
It's tiny.
You're so cute.
It's hard.
I can't fight a lot of battles here.
That's funny.
Next up is the Balloon Gum Challenge.
Tsutsui is running for president.
Three, two, one.
What's your speed? Speed is
100%.
One time, please.
Wipe.
I wiped it.
It hardens after you make one.
If you don't wipe it once when you spread it out
I see.
I'll have to teach you this.
Please do.
Three, two, one.
Oh, yeah.
That should puff it up.
Now that...
It has to be gradual.
It's Yoda coming out.
Three, two, one.
He's doing something.
Oh, it's so tiny.
It's over.
It's so tiny.
It's bad that there's a monitor here.
Don't look at it.
Please go back.
Next is Nakanishi's challenge.
It's so tiny!
This tournament is so low.
Lilia, you're a real pain in the ass.
What am I being forced to watch?I don't know what they make me watch.
I know you're itching to do it.
If anyone on your side of the room wants to gum up, just hang out there for a second.
Can you hold up the gum for me?
The next candidate was Inoue.
Three, two, one.
Good job.
Good luck.
Yes, yes, yes.
Tiny!
Why are you so tiny?
He's cute, but...
Next, Endo tries his hand.
Three.
Three... two... one...
One.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, it's over, but it took a moment, maybe even a second.
Well, there was a big one.
Let's have everyone on the dais go if they think they can make it.
That one looks great!
Okuda, Okuda, can you get a big one?
Yes, yes.
Wow! Winner! Winner!
Inoue, what are you doing? Here. Can I see something?
Inoue, what are you doing? Here. What are you doing making a big one here?
This way. I thought it was done.
I thought it was okay since it's done. I tried it and made a big one.
You're right.
What about the spilled sugar balloons? Then spilled sugar balloons?
Are you sure?
I'm not sure. It's too low. Okay.
Okay, let's go, please.
You're in first place.
But how can you say the level is too low?
But you won.
Well, well, well.
And the last Ikeda...
Don't laugh.
I think we did pretty well.
Not bad... maybe one of the top three.
And now, the results of the video judging...
The 4 winners and the 8th place finisher...
And the 8th place winner... here he is!
Nakanishi!
That's not good.
We're practically in last place.
That's right.
It's practically dead last!
I can watch it because it's cute... and I'd change the channel immediately.
And who's good? Hatsuki-san was good.
Hazuki was good. - She's amazing.
This... this... this...
The title of the new single is Monopoly.
The jacket photo is ready!
Tickets for the new mono live streaming are now on sale!
The ghost team won!
Yay!
We are so happy! Glad to hear it.
I'm glad.
Was it fun?
Yeah, it was a lot of fun.
It was great.
We got a lot of candy.
We ate a lot, didn't we?
We ate a lot. It was delicious.
So, please subscribe to our channel
Please subscribe to our channel.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.